<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Name>External Suit Reader [StationeersMods]</Name>
  <Author>vinus</Author>
  <Version>1.0.0</Version>
  <Description>
    [h1]External Suit Reader[/h1]
    [b]WARNING:[/b] This is a StationeersMods Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersMods plugin.
    See: https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods

    [h1]!!!! WARNING !!!![/h1]
    [i]saving is disabled by default, however you can enable it in the mod config menu. without saving, all channels are initalized at a default value of 0[/i]
    [b][u]this mod has changes for allowing ic10 scripts to write to Channel0-7, the mod has to modify save data in order to save it.[/u][/b]
    [b][u]this may or may not cause save corruption, so be warned. if you dont use saving it will be fine.[/u][/b]

    Makes the advanced suit have the ability to read the external atmosphere of which the suit is in.
    There are also many new things able to read and write to.

    Reading gas ratios is shown in the mod thumbnail.

    other stuff:
    you can read the total moles of the external atmosphere you are in. (use [b]TotalMolesOutput[/b])
    you can read the prefabhash of the object you are looking at. (use [b]TargetPrefabHash[/b])
    you can read the position of the object you are looking at. (use [b]TargetX, TargetY, TargetZ[/b])
    you can read the passed day number. (use [b]Time[/b])
    you can read the battery charge ratio directly. (use [b]Charge[/b])


    you can also go here to get the dll itself if you want to just put it in your bepinex/plugins folder:
    https://github.com/TerameTechYT/StationeersSharp/tree/development/Build/x64/Release
  </Description>
  <WorkshopHandle>3071985478</WorkshopHandle>
  <InGameDescription>
    <![CDATA[<size="30"><color=#ffa500> External Suit Reader </color></size>
<b>WARNING:</b> <color=#ff0000>This is a StationeersMods Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersMods plugin.</color>
See: <b><u><color=#00ccff>https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods</color></u></b>.
]]>
  </InGameDescription>
  <Tags>
    <Tag>Mod</Tag>
    <Tag>BepInEx</Tag>
    <Tag>StationeersMods</Tag>
  </Tags>
</ModMetadata>